imexamerica.com 2014-12-17

# IMEX America: Privacy Statement

### How we will use your personal information

This privacy notice applies to anyone entering information on our website, registering online for an IMEX exhibition, subscribing to our newsletter or making an inquiry or complaint to us.

This notice does not cover third party websites to which we provide links, which should be covered by their own privacy notices. The IMEX Group is not responsible for the content of third party websites.

### Who we are

Regent Exhibitions Ltd owns the IMEX in Frankfurt exhibition. IMEX America Ltd owns the IMEX America exhibition. Both Regent Exhibitions Ltd and IMEX America Ltd are incorporated in the UK. IMEX America Exhibitions Inc. is a US incorporated company which provides support services in the US to IMEX America Ltd. All are collectively known as the IMEX Group.

Regent Exhibitions Limited, The Agora, First Floor, Ellen Street, Hove, East Sussex, United Kingdom BN3 3LN. Company No. 4244004

IMEX America Limited (Address as above). Company No 7339316

IMEX America Exhibitions Inc., 415 Madison Avenue Floor 15, New York, NY 10017-7935 Incorporated in Delaware

### How we will use your personal information

We are committed to collecting and using your personal information fairly and transparently, so we will make it clear if we are collecting personal information from you or intend to use it for any purpose that is not obvious. 

We use the personal information that you provide to us for our internal purposes, such as responding to your requests for information, contacting you, conducting internal analyses, and processing and completing orders and event registrations.

The IMEX Group also reserves the right to compile, save, use within the scope of our activities, and analyse any and all data (contact and personal data, use history, etc.) that we collect from you through the Website.

We may disclose personal information to a third party, such as a law enforcement agency, if required to do so by law.

### Opt in preferences – the IMEX Group and third parties

When you submit personal information to us through the Registration Pages on this Website, you will be given an opportunity to opt in to receiving information from us and from selected third parties. When such permission is granted, we may provide lists containing your name, company, title, address, telephone number and/or email address to third parties and our affiliates for their direct and indirect marketing and promotional purposes, and we may use your personal information for the same purposes. 

The IMEX Group will not pass your personal information to any third party for marketing purposes without your consent.

If you initially elect to opt in to either the IMEX Group or third party mailing lists, and later decide that you would like to opt out, you may email us at [privacy@imexexhibitions.com](mailto:privacy@imexexhibitions.com?subject=IMEX%20Exhibitions%20Privacy%20Statement). Please keep in mind that although the IMEX Group strives to update our mailing list database as frequently as possible, it may take up to ten days to process email requests, during which time your information might be communicated to another party in connection with a mailing list. Additionally, you should be aware that any mailing lists that have been provided to third parties prior to your election to opt out cannot be retrieved by the IMEX Group, and you cannot retroactively opt out with respect to such third parties. 

### Sharing your personal information with vendors

We may share the personal information you provide to us with other companies we have hired to provide services for us. These companies – our vendors – are contractually bound to use personal information that we share with them only to perform the services we have hired them to provide.

### Security

We will take care to ensure that your personal information is secure. When we do provide mailing   
lists to third parties or vendors we enter into agreements with such parties requiring them to comply with all applicable laws, and prohibiting further distribution or disclosure of the lists to other parties.

### Transferring personal information overseas

Our website is hosted and backed up on a server in Germany.

We may transfer your personal information to countries outside the European Economic Area (where lower levels of data protection may apply) to make arrangements for any exhibition you have registered to attend, or in any other case where we have your specific consent.

### Your rights

You have the right to access personal information we hold on you.

You can ask us to correct any personal information we hold on you.

To review the information IMEX currently holds on you, please email [privacy@imexexhibitions.com](mailto:privacy@imexexhibitions.com?subject=IMEX%20Exhibitions%20Privacy%20Statement) and request to view your contact and demographic information.

### Changes to your personal information

Please let us know if any personal information you have given us changes, so we can keep our records up-to-date.

### Visitors to our website

We use Google Analytics to help us to improve our website. This uses cookies to collect information about how visitors reach and use our website, but does not identify any individuals. Other cookies are used to help you log in and use the site most effectively. By accepting this privacy policy you are giving your consent to the use of cookies on our website. See the [Cookies](http://www.imexamerica.com/about-us/cookies/ "Cookies") section of our website for more information.

Further information about the cookies used by Google Analytics is given at [Cookies and Google Analytics](https://developers.google.com/analytics/resources/concepts/gaConceptsCookies "Google and Cookies").

### Recording at exhibitions

Videos and photographs are taken at IMEX exhibitions and used to promote future events, including direct mail and email marketing, newsletters, press releases and broadcasts over the internet, through our broadcast partners, or via other broadcast services. CCTV and webcams are not used by our organization, although our exhibition venues may utilize them.

### Corporate transactions

If we sell or transfer the whole or part of our business or assets we may transfer personal information to the buyer or transferee.

### How to contact us

You can contact us with any questions or comments on this notice at [privacy@imexexhibitions.com](mailto:privacy@imexexhibitions.com?subject=IMEX%20Exhibitions%20Privacy%20Statement). For any other questions or comments, please see the [Contact Us](http://www.imexamerica.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us") section on our website.

### Changes to this privacy notice

We will regularly review and update this privacy notice and will ask for your consent before using your personal information in a way that is significantly different.

This notice applies to visitors to our websites from April 1, 2012, and was last revised on July 1, 2014.
